DenysPotapov

developer

contact

+38 050 330-20-57 **S** denys.potapov **in** denyspotapov

denys.potapov@gmail.com

skills

PHP, python, MySQL, JavaScript, HTML, SCSS

languages

bilingual Ukrainian/Russian intermediate English basic German

profile

I am a developer with over 9 years experience working on a variety of projects from conception to delivery. I am conversant in a wide range of technologies, now focused on web development (PHP, python), follow the latest industry trends with great interest (SCSS, HTML5). My approach is methodical but creative. I am comfortable working either independently or as part of a team.

education

2002–2008 **M.Sc. degree in Computer Science**Specialisation in computer systems and robotics

experience

2012—Present	barzo.com.ua Creating and launching a start-up company. Developing from the ground e-commerce platform (PHP, MySql, HTML, SCSS). Managing team of 3 freelancers.
2012—Present	Qport Creating a large network of digital signage systems (biggest project with 8000 screens). Integrating ERPsystem in retail stores (15 stores).
2009—2012	Qport Developing interactive screens software (python). Developing an ERP system for retail stores (1c ERP).
2008—2009	Physico-technological institute Development and integration of foundry process modeling system (Object Pascal) for perspective developments department institute of

(Object Pascal) for perspective developments department institute of metals and alloys of the National academy of science of Ukraine

Proling Office developer

Development of machine translation system ProlingOffice (C#) and it's

Development of machine translation system ProlingOffice (C#) an online version (ASP.NET)

awards

2005-2007

August 2014	IQLab Challenge	2 nd place
-------------	-----------------	-----------------------

PHP backend development

November 2013 UA Web Challenge V 3rd place

Backend development

Codingame oDesk Contest 5th place

python developers

skills

basic Objective-C, C++, Assembler

intermediate JavaScript, HTML, SASS

advanced PHP, python, MySQL

languages

native Russian/Ukrainian

intermediate **English** conversationally fluent

basic German basic words and phrases only

interests

blogging habrahabr.ru

Top-100 author in biggest Russian-speaking IT community

volunteer Running a code club

Code-club in Kyiv is a part of network of volunteer-led after school cod-

ing clubs for children aged 9-11

running